♪ [Kazumi Totaka - Mii Plaza] ♪
You look like Hitler...
Yes, I look like Hitler in his videos.
What, can it be longer?
How are you going to like that?
How do you know...?
Take it! With your hands! Come
take it! with your hands.
♪ [Lowercase - Kid Singing in Walmart] ♪
Hello, little creatures of the Lord!
How are you?
Today we are in... Norway.
And, for the first time,
I have brought...
to my partner...
friend...
and brother...
Bergen?
¿Be-Bergen?
'Wait, I have something here...
What- what will it be?
Bergen?
Won't it be-
Isn't that a bit of Bergen?
Bergen?
Ah, what a polar, arctic cold, huh?
It's too cold, my friend!
Look, look
If it has snowed and everything
Ha rent' eh? Ha horse
What do you think of Norway so far?
Now I love it, it's cold
Is it cold? Well, here it is.
O
Well, they have brought us, basically
eh... for an event of
ＧＯＤ ＯＦ ＷＡＲ
They had invited me and I said,
"I have to bring Mangel with me."
For the first time in Norway
For you to see, enjoy and feel.
Bergen?
You, it's not normal how fucking cold it is.
I have nipples...
that could cut concrete,
right now, that is
But well, as you know,
Norway...
it's like my...
my second home, so to speak,
why...
My mother is from here,
and I'm living here
I'm very excited
having brought Mangel, okay
and...
teach him some things about...
my culture...
From this, our culture...
Okay, so we are...
tomorrow,
that is, today
y
We are...
here with a lot of people
who are also youtubers and such,
and we're leaving...
to a strange place,
Okay, by boat...
We have here like a little map
Where are we going to go from here, let's see...
Well, that's basically the plan for today...
To do a lot of activities
on this site that appears here,
a... a Viking village
Look at my hair!
I look good there, man, but...
Here you come out fucking great
There you go-
Double vlog, guys
, doble vlog.
But you're whiter this way, huh?
Well, as you can see,
the game is inspired
in my lands, that is
There are the fjords, and that
and basically it's...
Well, it doesn't look the same now,
because everything is snowy,
but...
you know what I think...
very well, then
I think we're getting there now...
to the Viking village, okay?
¡A Michigan!
It's... it's close by
It's freezing cold, man.
I don't know how Kratos could go around here and
shirtless.
It should go with hard nipples, man.
You didn't explain that, huh?
They hadn't explained that to us!
They just made a presentation like
talking about the game and such, and...
And they haven't said anything about Kratos' nipples.
Nothing. Nothing.
Zero. Zero.
They are the ones that do not have a point.
ＯＯＦ
🅾🅾
Okay, we're on a boat now and
and how the hell didn't we think of this before?
do this.
♪ [Céline Dion - My Heart Will Go On] ♪
I'm the king of the fucking world!
And IIIIIIIIIIII
I am the king-
He's singing the Bodyguard song!
Hey, something's burning over there!
Something's burning there!
God...
We are arriving at the Viking village
and everything is burning, man
Everything is burning, man.
This is the song of my people, Mangel
[Viking songs]
Your family, Rubiu'
This is the song of my people
Is this your family?
Your grandfather, your cousin,
Your aunt...
Look, the one in the middle is you, 50 years old.
Is this it?
When you retire from YouTube already
It's your house
[Viking songs]
[Viking chants intensify]
You're seeing that, aren't you?
That's where they're going to sacrifice us to our gods.
Well, before their gods.
Him first.
Gosh, what realistic graphics!
Mother of God!
[dramatic music]
What have you done, damn it!
[dramatic music intensifies]
You killed your family!
[dramatic music intensifies more]
To your grandfather, to your cousin, to your aunt!
Son of a bitch!
Killer!
[dramatic music by Mahe intensifies]
Okay, so we've arrived.
We are in...
Thank you
OK?
I've never been here in my life.
Which is a part of Norway
It's kind of like up north, right?
But basically
It's the same as the rest of Norway, that is
It is full of fjords, and such
What you have here is great, man.
They have a fucking Viking ship, okay?
I think we're going to be able to ride it.
Okay, so this is the entry for...
from the area...
Viking, so to speak
We have here...
Hello!
Do you speak Norwegian?
In the.
In the...
I'm talking!
Do you speak Norwegian?
Good, good
Are you cold?
No, everything is fine.
Hello, traveler!
How can I help you today?
10 grams...
cooking
10 grams of emotion?
Those will be...
15 shekels.
Greetings, traveler.
How can I help you today?
I have potions,
I have food...
pieces...
and much more!
Sell.
A dragon!
I don't know what the hell happened to my hair,
but I look like a bitter now.
But let's go to this place...
"Tattoos & Face Paint"
Let's see what they do to us
Hi!
Would you like to wear face paint?
Yeah!
Yes? Come in!
This lady looked like an NPC
Hosts!
You look like Kratos, asshole!
Because I'm white!
The white one, there
¡Oh!
SOO
You're such a creep!
Because?
Because you look like Kratos, man.
You feel like you're going to blow my fucking head off right now.
Into [...]
Look, my grandfather!
Other!
Damn, he's pulling out his sword.
Cuidao' cuidao' cuidao'
You just completed the final mission!
Okay, the lady who painted our faces told us that...
in this booth here...
they put you or make you like a...
a drawing...
From your name...
in runic.
This is full of NPCs, huh?
cuidao'
hOi !!
Hi!
Where are you from?
I'm from Spain, but I can speak...
YOU CAN SPEAK!
I can speak ｎｏｒｓｋ
Can speak... Norwegian!
Yes, I can speak Norwegian.
Come in! Come in!
And?
Okay, this is easy,
it looks like an R
That's right, yes.
You are a great writer in the runic schools!
What I have learned today is worth it.
Of the one who teaches...
— Thank you. — Thank you.
— Hi — Hi!
I have learned runic.
These NPCs are very nice and very realistic.
Thank you so much!
Thank you, thank you!
Well, this seems to be like...
a lesson...
del "drumming"
Viking drums.
One, two, three, four
One, two...
One, two, three, four,
One, two, three, one!
One, d... ah!
One, two, three, four,
One, two, three,
One, two,
One, two, three, four,
One, two, three,
More or less! More or less!
Almost, almost, almost, almost!
I got it now, huh!
[Viking songs]
One, two, three, four,
One, two, three,
One, two,
One, two, three, four,
ｏｏｏｏｏｏｈｈｈ
One, two, three!
Long live Maicra!
Long live, long live, long live!
One, two, three, four!
Be, be, be!
Be!
Greetings, everyone! Spain!
Aha - hello!
Be!
Olé!
¡One, do-
Good morning
cracks...
machines...
bosses...
chickens...
Beasts...
Mastodons...
Stop it, you bastard, don't touch me-
No, how was it?
"Stop it, motherfucker, don't go pecking."
"Don't go pecking!"
Hey, stop it, you bastard, don't peck me!
Next test:
archery...
...and axe thrower.
Let's see what's cooking.
The people at PlayStation told me...
that this is like the hardest thing
to do ballistics,
Let's see if we can do it the first time.
Damn, man, it always goes to the left!
Ooohhh, almost!
¡Genial!
To... to the wild boar
There are two hundred of them!
Ｓ Ｏ Ｎ Ｄ Ｏ Ｓ Ｃ Ｉ Ｅ Ｎ Ｔ Ｏ Ｈ Ｒ Ｕ Ｂ Ｉ Ｕ Ｈ
To the wild boar, eh
He deserves it!
¡Oooooohhh!
Two hundred, because everything goes two hundred
There are two hundred of them
I made a hole in it, poor deer.
Okay, let's go in...
like a strange cave...
I don't know what's going to be in here, but...
Good morning
Good day
My goodness, they've worked hard, huh?
Fuck!
[music]
O
Son of a bitch!
Yes!
O
Stop, stop, stop! What-
Norwegian revenge!
Hello!
We are at Bergen Airport...
And I'm with Mangel...
Hello! I'm... Mangel,
yyy...
oh my god
I loved your city, huh?
I loved it
Did you love it?
It's my country
In general
I mean, your country, yes.
My country, yes
You know, Norway
The food is good...
Too pretty, too pretty, too pretty
The mountains and fjords are also beautiful...
The best thing I've ever seen, I swear.
I'm really telling you, I'm telling you
Bergen?
I think it was nice, okay?
We're going to say goodbye here.
Give it a like
¿600 mil likes?
No! A million?
Let people give the likes they want.
No, no, no, no, no
Give it a like, because this is special, okay?
Mangel and Rubius in...
That's it, give it a like
Mangel and Rubius...
— Country of... — Norway
♪ [The Turtles - Happy Together] ♪